judge I ask people from Russia how do you feel
судья у людей из россии спрашиваю как вы
about the war in ukraine
относитесь к войне в украине
what kind of war is going on in ukraine
какой войне которая идет в украине
now and in ukraine there is a war blow the
сейчас а в украине идет война удар
russian federation attacked ukraine for the
российская федерация напала на украину
first time it’s like this at
первый раз уж такое у
your house it’s forbidden war for
вас дома же это запрещено война за в
this criminal is responsible for
этом криминальный ответственна за вас
you  - in another way, this operation is called an early
по-другому это операция называется рано
special operation, yes,
спецоперацию да
to know this, or if you then I
это знать или если вы то мне от вас
worn out from you to this is not rape, this is a
износилась к это не изнасилование это
sexual special operation
сексуальная спецоперация
to the essence, the essence is the same taslam and it remains the
до суть суть же таслам и остается
terms you can juggle
терминами можно жонглировать
how you feel about this
как вы относитесь к этому
maniac, but the killing of people in Ukraine of the
маньяку а к убийству людей в украине
Russian Federation is an action  dimensional life,
российской федерации действо мерных жить
I deny
отношусь отрицать
it, that is, you think that Putin is not
то есть вы считаете что путин не
right to do that he led troops to
правильно сделать что вел войска в
Ukraine,
украину
well, look at the civilians you have been killing for
ну смотрите мирных жителей у вас убивали
8 years,
8 лет
actually, yes, well, in the Donbass and you generally
вообще-то да ну на донбассе и вы вообще
didn’t say anything on this topic, not
никто ничего не говорил на эту тему не
like you pretended to  you don't know anything
как вы делали вид что вы ничего не
so no
поэтому нет
people asked for help our president
люди попросили о помощи наш президент
came to the rescue
пришел на помощь
you understood your magic i.e. you came to
ты понял вашу магию то есть вы пришли
kill  to kill people because they killed
убивать людей из-за того что убивали
people there people and who in Mali Mariupol was
людей там людей а кого в мали мариуполе
generally killed for 300 ran away to you
вообще поубивали на 300 убежал к вы
killed, that is, the city was simply destroyed there
убили то есть там город уничтожены
and they were military but if your
просто и ляли по военно но если ваши
military Nazis they hide behind the backs of
военные нацисты они прячутся за спинами
ordinary citizens stop stop look here
обычных граждан стоп стоп смотрите вот
you  what city do you live in
вы в каком городе живете
here is a legend there is a military unit
вот сказание есть воинская часть
yes it is located in the city
да она находится в городе
in different ways so why do you have a
по-разному разному так почему у вас в
military unit in the city of kazan in the city
городе казани воинская часть в городе
they are somewhere in an open field
они где-то в чистом поле
about
о
pissing
мочиться
everything we have sit they are not sticks just
все имеем сидите их не палочки просто
heard behind the backs of civilians
заслушивается за спинами мирных жителей
so it breaks about such calculations here
так разбивается о такие рассчи вот
shocking here in your place everyone who is clean
эпатаж вот вашем месте весь кого чист
sometimes go in places psycho parents to the
иногда заходят в местах псих родители до
place of Anna’s
места заходов
calls days shorter than a foot in the field
анны days короче фут в поле часты
Ukraine is often drawn and so
нарисована украину и так сама двойку
you start the deuce for this and that and it’s a
начинаешь по то-то и оно-то
woman’s squeal and there it stands for the sake of  you don’t
женский визг а там стоит ради вы не
like clowns in Moscow defended what he
нравятся клоуны москве обороняла чего
insisted and in places, and here she is, and the
настоял и в местах и вот она и сразу
children’s buttons are immediately reaching out with a pen, but because
ручкой тянутся детей кнопочки а потому
it was to act and so it will turn out
что был действовать и так на получится
more until the
бильше до
appearance  kion and zombie
появления kion и зомби